accuranker.com 2019-10-01

# Privacy policy - What information we collect and how we use it

This privacy policy explains how AccuRanker uses and protects any information that you provide. We take your privacy seriously so we would like to let you know you what information we collect from you and how we use it. We might ask you to provide specific information by which you can be identified when using this website and our services. Information you provide will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

## What personal information we collect

We collect basic user profile information from users of AccuRanker’s site. We collect personal information from you that you voluntarily submit to us and that identifies you personally, such as your name, e-mail address, company name, address, phone number, and other information about yourself and your business.

Personal information also includes navigational information and payment information where such information can directly or indirectly identify an individual. Navigational information is information about your computer and your visits to this website such as your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit and pages viewed. We collect and process payment information from you when you subscribe to AccuRanker’s service, including credit card numbers and billing information, using third party service providers.

Third parties with access your personal information

AccuRanker uses various third party service providers, such as payment systems, CRM systems, email marketing services and other necessary service providers to help us provide services you. We may disclose some of the information about you to our third party service vendors with limited access to perform specific tasks and services on our behalf, such as credit card payments. We only work with companies who we trust to keep your information safe, and only share the minimum amount of information necessary to provide our services.

Cookies are very small text files that are stored on your computer when you visit some websites.

We use cookies to help identify your computer so we can tailor your user experience, track shopping basket contents and remember where you are in the order process. You can disable any cookies already stored on your computer, but these may stop our website from functioning properly.

Analysing data about web traffic helps us improve our website in order to tailor it to your needs using Google Analytics (see Google Privacy & Terms here).

The following is strictly necessary for the operation of our website: this website will remember that you are logged in and that your session is secure.

The following are not strictly necessary but are required to provide you with the best user experience and also to tell us which pages you find most interesting (anonymously): this website will offer chat support and track the pages you visits via Google Analytics.

## Why we collect personal information and how do we use it

We use the information we collect only in compliance with this Privacy Policy to provide you with a better service by understanding your needs.  
We send emails to our service users. You can unsubscribe from marketing and promotional emails at any time by using the ‘unsubscribe’ link in the email received. You will still be contacted regarding important information about our services.

Occasionally, we may contact you on behalf of business partners about a particular offer that may be of interest to you. In this case, we will not transfer your personal information to the third party.  
We will never sell your personal information to any third party.

We may use your personal information to improve your user experience by personalising our website, send you personalised offers and use your information to make the communication relevant for you.

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, or our treatment of your personal information, please contact hello@accuranker.com.

## Frequently Asked Questions​

Can I Upgrade My Account?

Yes, you can upgrade your account at any time. The remainder will automatically be accounted for on your new invoice. This applies to both monthly and annual subscriptions.

AccuRanker has a huge infrastructure and capacity. We can upgrade your account to fit all your needs, whether you need to track a few thousand or a few hundred thousand.

How Accurate is Your Data?

AccuRanker has servers in every country that we support, meaning we deliver 99.9% accurate data, both globally and at the local level.

Can I Import Data From My Previous Tool?

Yes – AccuRanker supports data import from numerous tools, see the complete list here. If your current provider isn’t listed, please contact support for assistance.

Will AccuRanker increase the price of my subscription?

No, AccuRanker will not force you to pay more for your subscription in the future. If the price of our subscriptions rises, it will only affect you if you decide to upgrade or downgrade your plan. Your current plan will always stay the same.

If I cancel my subscription or my trial runs out, what will happen to my account?

Your account settings, domains and keyword data will still be in the account, but it will be inaccessible until your subscription is eventually re-activated. We will also stop updating your rankings during this time.

Can I get a discount on my AccuRanker subscription?

No, the prices on our pricing page are the best we can offer and are therefore non-negotiable (unless you want to pay more 😉 ). This is to provide full transparency, as well as saving you time from having to negotiate with us to find the best price. The more keywords you track, the lower the price per keyword. This is also reflected in the pricing.

Can I jump from a monthly to a yearly subscription later on (and vice versa)?

Yes, you are able to manage this in the AccuRanker platform under the Account tab.

Do you have a refund policy?

Yes, if you are not satisfied with your purchase, AccuRanker has a 14 day refund policy from the initial purchase. To request this, simply write to us in the chat or at hello@accuranker.com.

Does AccuRanker charge more if I need to add more users?

No, with exception of the Basic plan (e.g. 500 keyword plan). From 1,000 keywords and above all AccuRanker plans include unlimited users
